(Leonard:)-Hey.
-Thanks for letting me come over.
(Howard:)Of course.
Please, come in.
(Emily:)I just wanted to say how sorry
I am about tonight, and...
...l want to make sure that we're okay.
(Raj:)Look, you and I haven't made
any commitments to each other.
(Sheldon:)I know.
I just felt like I needed to explain.
(Emily:)The guy I was
with did my last tattoo,
(Emily:)and he's been
asking me out for months.
(Emily:)I finally said yes
just to get it over with.
(Raj:)-It's okay.
-Really?
(Raj:)Well, I mean, yeah,
it freaked me out a little,
(Raj:)but that's my issue, not yours.
(Wil:)Wow.
(Emily:)If I saw you out with another woman,
I'd be pretty upset.
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Raj:)Not just for being upset,
but for believing that could happen.
(Emily:)Just so you know,
I'm not seeing anyone else.